<?xml version="1.0"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>Issaquah Tooth Whitening - www.issaquahdental.com</title>
<link>http://www.issaquahdental.com</link>
<description>Issaquah Valley Dental Care. We Treat and God Cures. 1660 NW Gilman Blvd Issaquah, WA 98027</description>
<language>en-us</language>

<item>
	    <title>Seattle Dentistry - www.issaquahdental.com</title>
		<link>http://www.issaquahdental.com/welcome_htm.htm</link>
		<description>Issaquah Valley Dental Care. We Treat and God Cures. Providing advanced cosmetic services. 1660 NW Gilman Blvd Issaquah, WA 98027</description>
		<guid isPermaLink = "true">http://www.issaquahdental.com/welcome_htm.htm</guid>
	</item>
	
	<item>
	    <title>Seattle  - Direct Adhesion Dentistry Pg3</title>
		<link>http://www.issaquahdental.com/procedures/direct-adhesion-dentistry-3.htm</link>
		<description>DIRECT ADHESION DENTISTRY: Anterior and Posterior Composite Restorations ANTERIOR COMPOSITE RESTORATIONS (WHITE FILLINGS) Tooth-colored filling placed on the chewing surface of back teeth allows dentists to place tooth colored restorative materials in molars and bicuspids with reliable success.</description>
		<guid isPermaLink = "false">http://www.issaquahdental.com/procedures/direct-adhesion-dentistry-3.htm</guid>
	</item>
	
	<item>
	    <title>Bellevue  - BriteSmile</title>
		<link>http://www.issaquahdental.com/glossary/branded-britesmile.htm</link>
		<description>What%u2019s one of the first thing a person notices about you? Your smile! A bright, white smile helps you look confident, approachable, healthy and vibrant. But did you know that over time, teeth naturally yellow and become discolored? It%u2019s true. If you smoke </description>
		<guid isPermaLink = "false">http://www.issaquahdental.com/glossary/branded-britesmile.htm</guid>
	</item>
	
	<item>
	    <title>Bellevue  - Smile Design</title>
		<link>http://www.issaquahdental.com/glossary/cosmetic-smile-design.htm</link>
		<description>Cosmetic dentistry isn&#039;t exactly a dental specialty. Those who call themselves cosmetic dentists do cleanings and drill cavities, too. They&#039;re just particularly interested in aesthetics, and they have extra training to do cosmetic procedures.</description>
		<guid isPermaLink = "false">http://www.issaquahdental.com/glossary/cosmetic-smile-design.htm</guid>
	</item>
	
	<item>
	    <title>Issaquah  - Extreme Makeover</title>
		<link>http://www.issaquahdental.com/glossary/cosmetic-extreme-makeover.htm</link>
		<description>Cosmetic dentistry is a crucial part of an Extreme Makeover. Improving your smile can be one of the easiest ways to improve your appearance. A great smile not only looks great but also makes you feel confident.
</description>
		<guid isPermaLink = "false">http://www.issaquahdental.com/glossary/cosmetic-extreme-makeover.htm</guid>
	</item>
	
	<item>
	    <title>Bellevue  - Dental Implants Pg2</title>
		<link>http://www.issaquahdental.com/sep/issaquah-dental-implants-2.htm</link>
		<description></description>
		<guid isPermaLink = "false">http://www.issaquahdental.com/sep/issaquah-dental-implants-2.htm</guid>
	</item>
	
	<item>
	    <title>Issaquah  - Sedation Procedure Instructions</title>
		<link>http://www.issaquahdental.com/procedures/issaquah-sedation-procedure.htm</link>
		<description>Do not eat or drink anything after midnight the night before surgery. Preoperative medications may be taken with a sip of water. You may brush your teeth before surgery, however, do not swallow any water.</description>
		<guid isPermaLink = "false">http://www.issaquahdental.com/procedures/issaquah-sedation-procedure.htm</guid>
	</item>
	
	<item>
	    <title>Seattle  - Non Metal Fillings</title>
		<link>http://www.issaquahdental.com/glossary/cosmetic-non-metal-fillings.htm</link>
		<description>Unlike inlays and onlays that are crafted in an outside lab, composite fillings can be made on-site and completed in only one office visit. Hard plastic that bonds to the tooth, composites are more conservative restorations than metal, requiring far less d</description>
		<guid isPermaLink = "false">http://www.issaquahdental.com/glossary/cosmetic-non-metal-fillings.htm</guid>
	</item>
	
	<item>
	    <title>Issaquah  - Lab Fabricated Adhesion Dentistry Pg3</title>
		<link>http://www.issaquahdental.com/procedures/lab-fabricated-adhesion-dentistry-3.htm</link>
		<description>After the successful placement of six porcelain veneers on his six upper front teeth, this young man emerged with a new smile and an improved level of self-confidence in his smile on the face after photo. Patient\'s concern: discolored fillings, worn edges, smile line.</description>
		<guid isPermaLink = "false">http://www.issaquahdental.com/procedures/lab-fabricated-adhesion-dentistry-3.htm</guid>
	</item>
	
	<item>
	    <title>Bellevue  - Lab Fabricated Adhesion Dentistry Pg4</title>
		<link>http://www.issaquahdental.com/procedures/lab-fabricated-adhesion-dentistry-4.htm</link>
		<description>Accidents happen and events occur...The plastic surgeon reduced the facial lacerations. The dentist was able to restore the remaining tooth structures without any significant further reduction of tooth structure. Note that with these new techniques, artificial looking caps are a thing of the past.</description>
		<guid isPermaLink = "false">http://www.issaquahdental.com/procedures/lab-fabricated-adhesion-dentistry-4.htm</guid>
	</item>
	
	<item>
	    <title>Seattle  - Teeth Whitening</title>
		<link>http://www.issaquahdental.com/glossary/cosmetic-teeth-whitening.htm</link>
		<description>Supervised bleaching procedures that are done in-office and at-home have become among the most popular treatment options. In some cases, the procedure is performed entirely in the office, using a light or heat source to speed up the bleaching process.</description>
		<guid isPermaLink = "false">http://www.issaquahdental.com/glossary/cosmetic-teeth-whitening.htm</guid>
	</item>
	
	<item>
	    <title>Issaquah  - Zoom Whitening</title>
		<link>http://www.issaquahdental.com/glossary/branded-zoom-whitening.htm</link>
		<description>The Zoom! In-Office Whitening System is a revolutionary tooth whitening procedure. It&#039;s safe effective and fast, very fast. In just over an hour, your teeth will be dramatically whiter. Zoom! Whitening is ideal for anyone looking for immediate results.</description>
		<guid isPermaLink = "false">http://www.issaquahdental.com/glossary/branded-zoom-whitening.htm</guid>
	</item>
	
	<item>
	    <title>Issaquah  - Digital Xrays</title>
		<link>http://www.issaquahdental.com/glossary/high-tech-digital-xrays.htm</link>
		<description>Digital X-rays are images that are taken digitally and loaded into a computer file especially for a specific patient.</description>
		<guid isPermaLink = "false">http://www.issaquahdental.com/glossary/high-tech-digital-xrays.htm</guid>
	</item>
	
	<item>
	    <title>Seattle  - Full Mouth Rehab</title>
		<link>http://www.issaquahdental.com/glossary/cosmetic-full-mouth-rehab.htm</link>
		<description>Starting with the techniques of neuromuscular dentistry, your doctor measures the position of your jaw and determines its ideal position. The process involves using a sophisticated computer program to record and define joint sounds, muscle activity during </description>
		<guid isPermaLink = "false">http://www.issaquahdental.com/glossary/cosmetic-full-mouth-rehab.htm</guid>
	</item>
	
	<item>
	    <title>Issaquah  - Restorative and Cosmetic Pg2</title>
		<link>http://www.issaquahdental.com/procedures/restorative-and-cosmetic-2.htm</link>
		<description>When teeth are missing, the conventional porcelain fused-to-metal fixed bridge is most often the treatment of choice. These bridge restorations are permanently fixed (cemented) in place and offer the patient long term function, durability and life-like cosmetics.</description>
		<guid isPermaLink = "false">http://www.issaquahdental.com/procedures/restorative-and-cosmetic-2.htm</guid>
	</item>
	
	</channel>
</rss>